Aondrae Hooks

900 Roanoke Dr Martinez Ca, 94553 510-692-5799 Aondrae.Hooks@gmail.com

To whom it may concern:

Computers and technology are my passion. I've been building and repairing computers for the last 3 years. I've built 10 PCs by myself and have repaired countless others. There is nothing in this world that brings me greater joy then working on computers. I would love to grow and expand my knowledge to help more people and to truly understand how every component operates to be able to fix every problem for anyone in need. I'm currently studying for my Comptia Networking+ certificate and would love to continue growing my portfolio and gain more certifications using the hands-on knowledge I gain from this experience. I would be very grateful if given the opportunity and would not disappoint.

Aondrae Hooks

Martinez, CA 94553 aondrae.hooks@gmail.com 510-692-5799

Willing to relocate to: Walnut Creek, CA - Concord, CA - Benicia, CA

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Warehouse Associate

DashMart - Concord, CA September 2021 to Present

- Picking and Packing orders. Pick orders that come through the app, pack the order and hand off to our drivers.
- Inventory and Spoilage Management. Stock receivables and manage inventory, including shelf life.
- Warehouse Organization. Clean and organize the warehouse.
- Delight Customers. Ensuring substitutions are approved with the customer.

Customer Service Representative

Old Republic Home Protection - San Ramon, CA September 2021 to Present

The Authorization Agent interacts regularly with our Plan Holders. They receive calls, and answer questions from Plan Holders and Service Providers concerning the warranty claim process. Call Center Authorization Agents must be able to determine coverage under the terms and conditions of the Plan and effectively communicate appropriate courses of action to Plan Holders and Service Providers. Duties include:

- Receive incoming calls from Plan Holders and Service Providers, logging pertinent information accurately and efficiently while on the telephone, and ensuring requests meets Plan guidelines (e.g. effective dates, coverage, limitations, etc.)
- Communicate effectively, asking pertinent questions to determine coverage
- Approve or deny service while educating callers as to Plan coverage and processes
- Evaluate bids to ensure suggested course of action is appropriate, and that parts/services are required and being provided at fair and reasonable prices
- Build customer loyalty by handling calls in a professional manner

Security Professional

Allied Universal Security Services, Systems and Solutions - San Francisco, CA March 2019 to March 2020

Responsibilities:

Secure premises and personnel by patrolling property; monitoring surveillance equipment; inspecting buildings, equipment and access points; permitting entry.

Ramp Agent

Southwest Airlines - Oakland, CA May 2018 to February 2019

Responsibilities:

Marshaling aircraft, loading/unloading and sorting freight and baggage, servicing the aircraft, assisting with pushback and towing, deicing and other duties as assigned.

Supervisor

UPS - Oakland, CA October 2015 to July 2018

Responsibilities:

Train and supervise daily activities of package handlers and ensure that all duties are assigned and accomplished safely and timely.

Skills Used

- Customer service skills (internal/external)
- Multi-tasking skills
- Perform general office tasks such as paperwork, typing, and/or use of a computer, filing, calculating and the use of telephone
- Good cognitive reasoning skills
- Self motivation
- Ability to direct the work of the other employees effectively
- Perform other functions that may be assigned
- Work cooperatively in a diverse work environment

Game Advisor

GameStop - Oakland, CA 2015 to October 2017

Responsibilities

Greet every guest.

Ring out, guest.

Answer any and all questions.

Maintain store organization.

Skills Used

Customer Service.

Goal Oriented Service.

Package Handler

United Parcel Service - Oakland, CA July 2015 to October 2015

Responsibilities

Assembles, lines and pads cartons, crates and containers manually to prepare them for shipment.

- Examines and inspects containers to make sure they are ready to be transported to the customer.
- Pulls out packages that are improperly labeled, sealed or backed for reprocessing.
- Handles fragile items and hazardous materials in a safe manner according to company and government rules and regulations.
- Places containers on proper conveyor belts and in chutes to go to the loading dock.
- Loads boxes, cartons and other packages onto trucks for delivery.
- Cleans the work area at the end of a shift

Accomplishments

Physically and mentally stronger

Skills Used

- Possesses excellent hand/eye coordination.
- · Has strong active listening skills.
- Demonstrates good critical thinking skills.
- Possesses strong reading comprehension skills.
- Has excellent decision making skills and the ability to make sound judgment.
- Displays exceptional time management and multi-tasking abilities.
- Demonstrates the ability to be mechanically inclined and detail oriented.
- Possesses the ability to be an effective troubleshooter.
- Has strong negotiation skills and the ability to speak clearly and articulately.
- Demonstrates extensive knowledge of math, weights and measures.
- Displays a clear understanding of safety and security issues.
- Has the ability to work independently with little direct supervision.
- Demonstrates the ability to accurately follow directions.
- · Exhibits strong concentration and memorization skills.
- Possesses data entry and other computer skills.
- Maintains good physical fitness to meet the demands of the job

Team Member

Jamba Juice - Oakland, CA February 2015 to July 2015

Responsibilities:

- Make a great first impression: smile and greet each guest.
- Show a sense of urgency and have a drop everything attitude.
- Get to know your guests and make them regulars.
- Become knowledgeable of Jamba's products and nutritional value to better understand your guest's needs and make a recommendation.
- Deliver a perfect product and a complete order every time.
- Say thank you to your fellow team members and make Jamba a fun and uplifting place to work.
- Look sharp and be on time for all scheduled shifts.
- Keep the store clean, organized, and looking great.
- Operate cash register and handle all cash transactions according to Jamba Cash Handling Policies.
- · Adhere to all Jamba food safety and security guidelines while maintaining company equipment.
- Do your best and strive for excellence in everything you do.
- Make a memorable connection and send each guest off with a smile.
- Make a lasting impression: Do whatever it takes to make the guest's experience the best a recommendation.

Server/Cashier/Dishwasher/Utility/Carver/Cook

Boston Market - Oakland, CA 2014 to 2015

Server/Cashier Responsibilities:

The first person the guests meet or see when they walk in the door. It's critical that you make them feel welcome.

Dishwasher/Utility Responsibilities:

To ensure and to deliver a safe, healthy and sanitary experience to every employee, and to all of the guests. Responsible to ensure that the guests can enjoy their food on clean plates, using clean silverware, that are served using clean serving pieces, and cooked in clean pieces of equipment.

Carver Responsibilities:

Skilled in cutting the chicken and carving the meats, making sandwiches and salads and presenting them on the plate for each guest.

Cook Responsibilities:

Virtually single handedly responsible for making sure that the restaurant has all of the hot, fresh, gourmet side items, pot pies, soups and other products available at all times that we are open.

Education

High school diploma

Dewey Academy - Oakland, CA 2014 to 2015

Skills

- Customer Service (4 years)
- Sales (2 years)
- Hard Working (10+ years)
- Motivated (2 years)
- Multi-Tasking (10+ years)
- Management (3 years)
- Heavy Lifting (4 years)
- Warehouse Experience (4 years)
- Surveillance
- Load & Unload
- Security
- Delivery Driver Experience
- · Problem-solving
- Team Work
- Freight Experience
- Flexibility
- Reliability
- Vehicle Maintenance
- Order Picking
- Pallet Jack
- Packaging

Security Guard

Driver's License

First Aid Certification

Assessments

Package Delivery Driver — Highly Proficient

October 2019

Interpreting instructions, reading maps, and solving problems.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Automotive Maintenance — Proficient

February 2020

Knowledge of vehicles, vehicle maintenance, and repairs.

Full results: Proficient

Security Guard Skills — Proficient

August 2019

Assessing risks, enforcing security standards, and handling complaints.

Full results: Proficient

Supervisory Skills: Motivating & Assessing Employees — Highly Proficient

May 2020

Motivating others to achieve objectives and identifying improvements or corrective actions.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Work style: Conscientiousness — Highly Proficient

May 2020

Tendency to be well-organized, rule-abiding, and hard-working

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.